Sullivan, Adolph Alcoholism Files 5891
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Adolph Sullivan Alcoholism Files
1971-1988
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Sullivan, Adolph
5891
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5725211
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 21, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Alcoholism and employment; Sullivan, Adolph
5725211
- ALMACA, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- ALMACA Occupational Alcoholism Program Study, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- ITT & ALMACA, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ALMACA, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Americans Against Union Control of Government & ALMACA, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ALMACA, 1970-1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Sixth Annual ALMACA, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Community Council of Greater New York & ALMACA, 1971-1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- ALMACA, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Annual Meeting (ALMACA), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- ALMACA Membership (), 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- ALMACA - Labor, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Sixth Annual ALMACA Western Regional Conference, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- ALMACA, 1978-1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- ALMACA President's Address, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Folklore & Facts about Employees with Alcoholism, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- ALMACA - Ex Comm. Mtg., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Scope and Contents
  Atlanta, November 10-11, 1974
- ALMACA - Chapters, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- ALMACA, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- ALMACA Membership Applications (Box 1, Folder 20)
- ALMACA - Consortia, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- ALMACA Corporate Campaign, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- ALMACA - General, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- ALMACA Personnel, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- ALMACA - Annual Meeting, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- ALMACA - Nominating Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- ALMACA - General, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- ALMACA - By-Laws, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- ALMACA Grant, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 29)